He comes from a police background,
after all.
Chief,
I'm worried...
With that thing holding him in check,
he has no choice but to work for me.
Chief, he is here.
[Eclipse in the Lost City]
[Episode 7]
Kill me.
Chief,
I beg you.
Kill me. Kill me.
Chief, he is here.
[Xu Qingdao, Chief of Shisha Gang]
Officer Shen is here.
Chief.
I just took care of a traitor.
Did it scare you?
At the police station,
all you usually do is slam a few desks
and smash a few cups.
We're a rough bunch here.
You're joking, Chief.
How could I walk through
the Shisha Gang's doors
without getting my hands bloody?
You're straightforward.
Then I'll get straight to the point.
Hui.
This is something new we got
from the Westerners.
It's also the ticket into the Shisha Gang.
Once you're injected with it,
the poison will flare up every full moon.
If you're not strong enough,
the pain could kill you.
As long as you behave,
you'll get a maintenance dose
every 2 weeks.
However,
if anything goes wrong...
This is what will happen to you.
How about it, Officer Shen?
Wanna think about it?
Is this enough
to satisfy you, Chief?
Tianbai.
Sit.
Tianbai,
you don't blame me, do you?
In times like these,
no one has it easy.
You have to leave yourself a way out.
Don't you agree?
I understand.
It's all for the Shisha Gang.
Good.
You really are a smart man.
Then I can trust you
to handle this.
Go ahead.
In three days,
the Shisha Gang
will be moving a shipment of arms
to sell to those soldiers.
If they're an army,
why would they be short on weapons?
They're no regular army.
Just a bunch of thugs and bandits
taking advantage of the chaos,
looting and killing wherever they go,
and fighting over territory.
Hui has already made the arrangements.
But he's reckless.
I need you to keep an eye on him.
Word must not get out.
Remember,
make sure the goods get there safely.
Yes.
Then prepare well.
[Dashijie]
Buddies.
Drink all you want tonight.
Don't you dare hold back on spending!
Drink!
Okay!
I'm so useless.
I've let the Qingtian Gang
and the old man down.
Isn't this Young Master Lu?
You really are useless.
Go home and cry to your mama.
You...
Come on.
Don't forget the mission.
Don't cause trouble.
I don't need you to teach me.
Shen Tianbai.
Seeing me like this,
are you happy?
You're drunk.
Young Master, are you all right?
Young Master.
Zhuque has no reason to lie.
But I still believe
the old chief wouldn't have
transported drugs willingly.
Someone must have forced him.
I believe it, too.
I'm going to get to the bottom of this,
no matter what.
Shen Tianbai was commended for his work
and stole Wu Ren's thunder,
so Wu Ren set him up and got him kicked out
of the police force.
He wanted revenge,
so he turned to Xu Qingdao.
The Shisha Gang had a condition, too.
To join,
he first had to prove his loyalty
by getting rid of someone
who could expose them.
And that person was Zhuque,
the mole inside our Qingtian Gang.
That's why he faked his amnesia,
went undercover around me,
and put on this whole act.
Shen Tianbai,
you really know how to bend
when you have to.
Right.
You've always been this kind of person.
Back then, it was to get an education.
Now, it's for revenge.
Drug trafficking.
If that batch of goods was really drugs,
then Shen Tianbai shooting him
was understandable.
Since the drugs are related
to the Shisha Gang,
then maybe Shen Tianbai joining
the Shisha Gang isn't such a bad thing.
Young Master,
what should we do next?
Help Shen Tianbai rise through the ranks.
Why are you still helping him?
He is a catfish.
Put a catfish in the water,
and it'll stir things up.
Once Shen Tianbai enters the game,
he's bound to muddy the waters.
Once the waters are muddied,
we'll have our chance to move in.
That bastard Hui.
He's usually so stingy.
But today,
he's suddenly spending like crazy.
There must be a big shipment.
Soot.
Rust.
Train station.
You, Shen,
are you looking down on me?
I'm telling you.
As long as I'm here,
I won't let even a mosquito get past me.
Who could possibly steal this shipment?
This is the chief's order.
The goods are in the carriage.
Go see for yourself.
Who did this?
Hui, over here!
Lure the tiger away from its lair.
What a coincidence.
Officer Shen.
No.
That's not right.
You're not an officer anymore.
You're just a dog kept by the Shisha Gang.
It's too late.
There's no time.
You didn't hijack the goods.
The goods are still in the carriage.
Smart.
But now,
the goods are ours.
When would I have had time
to move all that cargo?
I just switched out a few boxes
on the outside,
and Hui fell for it.
Why go to all this trouble
just to pull this off?
Why go to all that trouble
to infiltrate the Shisha Gang?
Where are the goods?
Spare my life, Chief.
It's all Shen Tianbai's fault.
He didn't keep a close eye on the goods.
Lu Ye found out about it.
He might be involved in it, too.
You sure know how to keep your cool.
As for the leak,
the innocent have nothing to fear.
As for that shipment,
it might not be such a bad thing.
What do you mean?
There's a problem
with that batch of goods.
Look, Chief.
There are scratches on these bullets.
They'd have to be removed and reloaded
to leave marks like these.
That means this ammo has been used before.
Did someone skim a little off the top,
and that's how this happened?
Those thugs with guns
are fighting over territory.
They're not people we want to mess with.
If they find out about this,
they'll come after us for it.
Now that the Qingtian Gang
has taken the shipment,
they've taken the fall for us instead.
So what do you suggest we do next?
Replace it with a better shipment.
Do you have another source?
I still have a few connections
from my years on the force.
As long as we're willing to pay enough,
we can make anything happen.
I'll leave this matter to you.
Yes, Chief.
I'll get in touch with them right away.
Go take your punishment.
Yes.
Master.
I've found it.